(Sheldon:)Fine.
LEONARD:
Yeah, okay, I see him.
(Leonard:)It looks like
they're having a nice time.
(Leonard:)I wish I could hear
what they're saying.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, I should've brought
(Bernadette:)my parabolic microphone.
(Penny:)Your what?
Nothing. Not important.
(Dave:)So you've never
been married?
(Amy:)No. I mean,
to be completely honest, I've...
(Amy:)I've only been
in one long-term relationship.
(Dave:)Oh. What happened with that?
(Amy:)That's a good question.
(Amy:)After five years,
(Amy:)it was just feeling like
more work than it should be.
(Dave:)Oh, that's too bad.
(Dave:)Was he a neurobiologist
like you?
(Amy:)No. He's a theoretical physicist
(Amy:)at Caltech.
(Dave:)I love teaching math, but
that would be my dream job.
(Dave:)What's his focus?
(Amy:)Um... used to be string theory,
now it's dark matter.
(Amy:)But... let's
not discuss Sheldon.
(Amy:)Let's get back to you.
(Dave:)Wait, you're not talking
about Dr. Sheldon Cooper?
(Amy:)I'm trying not to.